

MARCELA PETROLI

Front-end Web Developer

My Contact

Madrid, Spain

LinkedIn 🔗

GitHub 🔗

Portfolio 🔗

Technologies

REACT | | JAVASCRIPT | | JEST

NODE.JS | | EXPRESS | | SQLITE

HTML5 || CSS3 || SCSS || ZEPLIN

GIT || GITHUB || VSCODE || SLACK



Experience working within an Agile/SCRUM environment

Languages

Portuguese Native

English Bilingual proficiency Spanish Bilingual proficiency Italian Elementary proficiency

Education Background



TOEFL Preparation American Academy of English - San Francisco, USA

2016 - 2018



General English Program (C2) Embassy - San Francisco, USA 2015



Psychology Undergraduate Degree Unochapecó - Chapecó, Brazil 2009 - 2014

About Me

As a junior, I am committed to rely on my strongest traits - high adaptability, attention to detail, and resourcefulness - to constantly seek out new challenges and opportunities for growth and development. I am thrilled by the chance to receive the guidance of experienced professionals, and to be in an environment that challenges and inspires people to innovate.

Programming Experience

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP, ADALAB - Madrid, Spain Sept - Dec 2022

- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Flexbox, Grid, responsive design.
- JavaScript (ES6) and APIs.
- SPA with React.
- Basics of Node.js, Express and SQLite.
- Git for version control.
- · Remote work.
- Pair programming.
- Projects under Scrum framework and Agile methodology.
- Unit testing with Jest.

PROJECTS

⊗ STAR CARDS | | **⊗** BREAKING BAD | | **⊗** GUESS MY NUMBER

COURSES

- [In-Progress] The Complete JavaScript Course 2023: From Zero to Expert!, Udemy
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures, FreeCodeCamp, 2022
- Scratch and Computational Thinking, KeepCoding, 2022
- Professional Course of Git and GitHub, Platzi, 2022

Professional Experience

English Teacher, Canterbury English - Madrid, Spain 2019 - 2022

Child Care, +60 families - San Francisco, USA 2015 - 2019

Administrative Assistant, Foods Parnoff - Chapecó, Brazil 2008 - 2015